快点 出门啦
Come on, let's go.
我们要早点去 预留点多一点时间
We're gonna need a little more time
过机场的安检 因为我确信
at the airport security because I'm pretty sure
他们肯定会多留你一会儿
that they're gonna wanna patch you down.
曼尼这周末在他爸爸那
Manny is with his father for the weekend
所以我和杰要飞去拉斯维加斯度周末
so Jay and I are flying to Vegas.
我有点左右为难 因为我既想和歌洛莉亚过二人世界
I'm a little torn because I want alone time with Gloria,
又想揉揉曼尼的头 求得在赌场的好手气
but I also like rubbing Manny's head for good luck.
我得给克莱尔发封邮件
I just need to send this e-mail to Claire
解释一下我为什么不参加下周的糕饼义卖了
why I'm not working on the bake sale next week,
但我又不能告诉她真正的原因
but I can't say the real reason.
为什么
Why not?
因为每次她负责这些事的时候
Because she drives me crazy
都让我很抓狂
when she's in charge of these things.
好吧 我们还要赶飞机 所以我就来帮帮你吧
Okay. We got a flight to catch, so let me help you out here.
好
Okay.
把你想跟她说的话告诉我
You tell me what you want to say to her,
我帮你改的委婉一些
and I'll help you find a nice way to say it.
我想说
I want to say...
我不能去参加糕饼义卖了
I can't work on the bake sale
因为你是一个专横的控制狂
because you're a bossy control freak
还瞧不上我做的纸杯蛋糕
that looks down on my cupcakes
虽然你自己做的柠檬方形蛋糕干的要命
even though your lemon squares were very dry.
写好了 快吧
Done. Okay?
你看这个怎么样
How's this?
亲爱的克莱尔 我不能参加糕饼义卖了
"Dear claire, I can't work the bake sale
因为你是一个专横的控制狂 还瞧不上
because you're a bossy control freak who look down --"
真幽默 杰
Very funny, Jay.
我 我 刚才那呼呼的声音是怎么回事
I -- I -- why the whoosh?
哪去了 电子邮件哪去了
Where is -- where is the e-mail?
已经发送了 把它弄回来
It sended! Ay. Make it come back.
我不知道怎么把它弄回来
I don't know how to make it come back.
这下她会看到这封邮件
Now she's gonna read it,
然后认为是我写的
and she's gonna think it's from me!
严格来说 确实是你写的
Well, technically, it was from you.
走吧 出发了
Come on, let's hit the road.
已经发送了
It sended.
求求你回来吧
Please come back.
我们很喜欢这个街区 但有时候
We love our neighborhood, but sometimes the last thing
最讨厌的事是在堵了半天车 好不容易开回家之后
you want to do after fighting traffic
还得再开车出门吃饭
is get back in the car to go out to eat.
而步行范围内唯一的一家餐馆
And the only restaurant within walking distance
是沙威玛城
is Shawarma City.
两个沙威玛套餐 要猪肉还是鸡肉
Two Shawarma combo. Meat or chicken?
一个猪肉 一个鸡肉
Uh, one meat. One chicken.
鸡肉那份能不能都用白肉啊
And can you make the chicken all white meat?
三十二号 收银柜台付款
Number 32. Pay cashier.
好吧 你根本没回答我嘛
Okay, that's not an answer.
然后 奇迹发生了
Then a miracle happened.
城里最热门的新餐馆
Uh, the hottest new restaurant in the city
阿米莉亚 在两个街区外
opened up two blocks away --
开了一家分店
Amelia's.
但有个问题
But there was a problem.
五点十五分有位子
They can take us at 5:15...
我们是七老八十吗 这么早吃饭
What are we, 80?
我们是二十几岁的小伙子吗 半夜才吃饭
What are we, 20?
接下来 第二个奇迹
Then...miracle number two.
莉莉学前班里一个同学的妈妈
Turns out one of the mothers at Lily's pre-school
就是阿米莉亚本尊
is none other than Amelia herself.
所以我们约了她的儿子杰克逊一起玩
So we arranged a play date with her son, Jackson,
借机来取悦阿米莉亚
where we would, you know, charm Amelia.
好了
Okay.
史上最重要的游戏聚会
The most important play date ever,
所以你得表现出耀眼的一面哦 小甜心
so I'm really gonna need you to sparkle, sweetie.
我会像国庆日那天的烟火一样耀眼
Oh, I'm gonna sparkle like it's the 4th of July.
我是冲莉莉说的
I was talking to Lily.
今天是我们爸妈的结婚纪念日
It's our parents' anniversary,
我们准备把早餐给他们送到床头 给他们一个惊喜
so we're surprising them with breakfast in bed.
给他们买什么礼物 他们都不会喜欢的
They're impossible to buy for...
我们是这么想的
We think.
但我们也没买过
We've never really tried.
好了 准备好了吗
Okay. Ready?
一 二 三
One, two, three...
惊喜啊啊啊
Surpri-i-i--
不 不
Oh. Oh! No! No!
不 不 不
No! No! No!
-对不起 -什么都没发生
- I'm sorry! - Nothing's happening!
我的天啊
Oh, my god.
没错 孩子们撞见我们了
Yeah, our kids walked in on us.
-委婉地说 我们当时正在做爱 -天啊
- We were, as they say, "having sex." - Oh, god.
这一点也不委婉啊 菲尔
That's not a euphemism, Phil.
我们当时确实也就是在做爱
It's exactly what we were doing -- having sex.
还当着孩子们的面
In front of our children.
我们开始的时候他们又不在
Well, they weren't there when we started.
的确
No.
事实上 我们刚开始的时候 你也不在状态
In fact, you weren't even there when we sta...
天啊 天啊
Oh, my god. Oh, my god.
没什么大不了的 没准他们什么都没看见呢
It's okay. Maybe they didn't see anything.
亲爱的 他们尖叫 还把一托盘的早餐都扔了
Sweetie, t-they screamed, they dropped a tray of dishes,
然后就像屁股着火了一样地冲出去了
and then they ran out of here like they were on fire.
你才像着火一般火辣呢 女士
You were on fire, lady.
不是吧 你还有心情
Really? You're still going?
请原谅我认为
Well, forgive me for thinking
你如此激情的表现应该得到夸奖
your zesty performance deserves some praise.
菲尔 咱们的孩子现在正在楼下
Phil, our children are downstairs right now,
心灵上可能受到了巨大的创伤
and they are probably traumatized.
拜托 肯定没那么严重
Oh, come on. I'm sure it's not that bad.
我还是能看到
I can still see it!
我不敢相信刚刚发生的一切
I can't believe that just happened!
-他们刚才在干什么 -什么都没干
- What were they doing? - Nothing!
不管是什么都好 看上去老爸要赢了
Whatever it was, it looked like dad was winning.
是那个 他们在做那个
It! They were doing it!
他完全不明白你在说什么
He has no idea what you're taking about.
-性爱吗 -没错
- Sex? - Yes!
我知道性爱是什么 艾丽克斯
I know what sex is, Alex.
就是一男一女脱掉内衣
It's when a man and a woman take off their underpants
然后上床
and then get into the bed.
别再说了
Stop talking!
再给克莱尔打一次
Try Claire again.
手机没信号
I'm not getting a signal.
放松 我们会联系上她的
Relax. We'll get her.
矮子跟我说拉斯维加斯有一家餐厅
Hey, shorty told me about this restaurant in Vegas
在餐厅的正中
that's got a three-story wine tower
有个三层的红酒塔
right in the middle of it.
给客人倒酒的服务生绑着钢索飞来飞去
The guy who gets your wine flies around on a wire.
就像小飞侠彼得潘一样
Like the "Peter Pan".
不 不是像彼得潘
No. Not like the "Peter Pan".
这个地方档次很高
This is a high-end place.
是吗 世界上所有高级的餐厅里
Oh, yeah, because all the finest restaurants in the world
都有人拉着钢索飞来飞去
have people flying around on wires.
以前有个日本人把虾扔到你盘子里
You know, you used to go bananas
你都会抓狂到上蹿下跳
when a Japanese guy flipped a shrimp onto your plate.
你再看看你现在这副刀枪不入的样子
Now look at you.
-再给她打一次 -好吧
- Try her again. - Fine.
再跟你说一次 那餐厅不是像彼得潘那样的
And just so you know, it's not like Peter Pan.
那些服务生不会穿紧身裤什么的
I mean, nobody wears tights or anything.
如果他们什么都不穿
Well, if they're not wearing anything,
我可不想让他们在我的食物上飞来飞去
I don't want them flying over my food.
喂
Hello.
菲尔 是我 能让克莱尔接电话吗
Phil, it's me. Can I talk to Claire?
好的 稍等 杰
Yeah. One second, Jay.
-是你爸 -不不不 不接
- It's your dad. - No. No, no. Can't. Unh-unh.
她现在不想说话
She doesn't want to talk right now.
-完蛋了 -为什么
- Ay, no. - Why not?
她有点伤心过度
Uh, she's a little too upset.
菲尔 让她接电话
Phil, put her on.
他说他想
He says he wants to --
把电话挂掉
Hang up the phone.
抱歉 杰
I'm sorry, Jay.
她让我挂电话
She says I have to go.
虽然她是我亲生闺女
You know, she's my daughter and everything,
但那小子真该有点骨气
but that guy seriously needs to grow a pair.
我们尽力了
Well, we tried.
拉斯维加斯 我们来啦
Vegas, here we come.
掉头
Turn around the car.
我这是自愿掉头 可不是被你逼的
Only 'cause I want to.
你们家太漂亮了
This is a-a beautiful home.
我超六十年代复古风
I love the throwback to the '60s.
只不过如果现在真是六十年代的话
Although if this was the '60s,
我们就是一对"坚定的独身主义者"
we'd be a couple of "confirmed bachelors",
则莉莉会是一只约克夏
and Lily would be a Yorkie.
而我则会继续被困在无爱的婚姻中
And I'd still be trapped in a loveless marriage.
艾米莉亚
Oh, Amelia.
你真风趣
Oh, you are funny!
我真的很喜欢你们
I really like you guys.
我还没有时间
I mean, I haven't had a lot of time
去见其他的家长
to meet the other parents.
我是单身妈妈 工作又忙
You know, single mom, hectic work schedule...
艾米莉亚 你是做什么工作的
Now, what do you do, Amelia?
我有几家餐厅
I own a few restaurants.
我最近在附近又开了一家
I just opened one nearby.
天呐 就是那家艾米莉亚餐厅吗
Oh, my gosh. Are you that Amelia?
天呐
Oh, my gosh!
我们听说那家餐厅很棒
We've heard wonderful things about the restaurant.
那里生意一定很好
It must be doing well.
我们一直都订不到位子
We can never seem to get a r -- a reservation.
-都进不去 -进不去
- Can't get in. - Can't.
这事好办
Oh, well, that's no problem.
下次你打电话时 就告诉他们
The next time you call, just tell them --
等一下
Oh. One second.
不好意思 告诉他们什么
Oh, I'm sorry. Tell them what?
喂
Hello?
你给他看了吗 他说什么
Well, did you show it to him? And what did he say?
好的 等一下
Okay. Uh, hold on a second.
我换个电话
I'm gonna switch phones.
不好意思 是餐厅的事
I'm sorry. It's the restaurant.
我失陪一下
Excuse me just a minute.
你刚才叫我们在订位时跟他们说某句话的
You said to tell them something.
你听见了吗
Did you hear that?
等我们知道该说什么了 就有特权了
When we know what to say, we're in.
太让人激动了
Oh! This is very exciting.
我还从没在餐厅里享受过特权
I've never had an in at a restaurant before.
也许我们一到 他们就会在门口迎接我们 还叫得出我们的名字
They'll probably greet us at the door by our names,
然后把我们带到我们最爱的桌前
show us to our favorite table...
我们可以随意变换菜单
They'll let us play fast and loose with the menu,
晚餐时点午饭的食物 午餐时点晚餐的食物
order lunch things for dinner, dinner things for lunch!
-没事 没事 没事 -卡梅隆
- It's fine. It's fine. It's fine. - Cameron!
-没事 -别动了
- It's fine. - Stop moving.
你还在吗
You there?
让他接电话
Put him on the phone.
是婴儿监护器 要关掉吗
Oh, that's the baby monitor. Should we turn it off?
你是哪位
Who am I speaking to?
好吧 坎贝尔先生
Well...Mr. Campbell,
你要把厨房那个非常贵的工作台面换掉
you need to replace the extremely expensive countertop
上次叫你手下的笨蛋工人来修冰箱
that one of your incompetent workers clearly ruined
结果他却把工作台面弄坏了
when he was supposed to be fixing the refrigerator.
这就是她这么成功的原因
Okay, this is why she's so successful.
严厉但却镇定
She's tough but calm.
因为我不是白痴
Because I'm not an idiot!!
我可是法律学毕业的
As is evidenced by my law degree,
你要是不在接下来的七十二小时内
which I will happily dust off and use to crush you in court
把它给我修好 换掉
if you don't fix it, replace it,
或是开赔款支票给我的话 我就上法庭告死你
or send me a check in the next 72 hours.
这样吧 你呆在那
You know what? Stay right there.
不要走
Don't move.
装作你刚才什么都没听见一样
Act like you weren't listening.
怎么装
What does that look like?
很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
我得去一下餐厅
I have to run down to the restaurant for a minute.
我都不好意思说出口
I really feel terrible asking,
但是你们介不介意
but do -- would you guys mind --
-没问题 我们会帮你照看孩子 -好的
- Oh, it's not a problem. We'll watch the kids. - Okay.
没错 你去照料
Oh, yes, you go take care
你那间我们迫不及待
of that fabulous restaurant of yours
想要挤进去的餐厅
that we cannot wait to try.
艾米莉亚 我们预约时要说什么
And when we do call, Amelia, you said to --
杰克逊 妈妈一会就回来
Jackson, mommy will be right back.
真是太谢谢你们了
Okay. Thanks, you guys, so much.
我欠你们个大人情
I owe you big time.
听到了吗
Did you hear that?
她说欠了我们很大的人情
She owes us big time.
拉斯维加斯那间斟酒服务生挂着钢丝
You know, she also has that restaurant in Las Vegas
飞来飞去的餐厅也是她开的
where the sommeliers fly around on wires.
天呐 莉莉 谢谢你这么讨那边那位
Oh, my gosh. Lily, thank you for being such a trouper
不说话的小家伙的喜欢
with Mr. Personality over there.
我要好好地奖励你一下
I'm gonna get you a treat.
一盒果汁漏了 里面都湿了
Oh, a juice box broke in here. It's all wet inside.
你用得着那么大惊小怪吗 只是一片尿片
Will you stop gasping? It's just a diaper --
好吧 我们得想个计划
Okay. We need a game plan.
我们要排练一下到底要说什么
We need to rehearse exactly what we're gonna say
因为当我的宝贝孩子们用批判
because that is the only way I'm gonna hold it together
和厌恶的眼神望着我时
when my babies are looking at me
那是唯一能让我不会崩溃的办法了
with judgment and disgust.
首先 他们一直都是那样看我们的
First of all, that's how they always look at us.
菲尔
Oh, Phil.
其次 他们受的创伤没有你想象的那么大
Secondly, this isn't as traumatic as you think.
亲爱的 我有一次也曾撞见我爸妈做爱
Honey, I walked in on my parents having sex once.
那简直 太糟糕了
It was -- oh -- awful.
我甚至没法把那个画面从我的脑海里抹去
I can't even get the image out of my mind.
克莱尔 我们不像你的父母 咱俩状态好多了
Claire, we're not your parents. We're in much better shape.
好吧 你知道最糟糕的是什么吗
Okay. You want to know the worst thing?
他们连谈都不跟我谈
They didn't even talk about it.
他们就让那件事悬在那
They just let it hang there.
我不会那样对我们的孩子
I'm not gonna do that to our kids.
菲尔
Phil, this --
这是我们作为家长的关键性时刻
this is a defining moment for us as parents.
我们对这件事的处理方式
How we handle this could shape how they feel
会影响他们余生对性和亲密的看法
about sex and intimacy for the rest of their lives!
克莱尔 亲爱的
Claire. Honey.
亲爱的 只要咱俩不小题大做 这就不是什么大事
Honey, this is only a big deal if we make it a big deal.
这件事的基调是咱俩定的 冷静对待就是了
We set the tone here. So let's just play it cool.
就把这当成是一个有趣的大混战
Act like it was a big, funny mix-up.
说几个笑话 缓和一下气氛
Crack a few jokes. Lighten the mood.
笑话
Jokes.
怎样的笑话
What kind of jokes?
这是
Well, this is...
我先随便举个例子
I'm just spitballin' here, but --
如果我说 敲门敲门
What if I was all, "Knock, knock"...
他们会说 是谁啊
and they were like, "Who's there"?
我就说 不想撞到
And I was all, "Someone who doesn't want to see
自己父母嘿咻的人
their parents doing it.
所以我们才敲门
That's why we knocked".
当然这还要修改一下
Again, this is -- this is very rough.
他们怎么还在楼上
Why are they still up there?
嘿咻一般要多久
How long does sex take?
天呐 不要说了
Oh, my god. Stop talking.
你们俩注意到了吗
Did you guys notice
老爸刚才的表情就像是
that dad had the same look on his face
看到了一款新车一样
as when he smells a new car?
我要离开
I need to leave.
我要去露营
I need to go to camp.
他们下来的时候肯定会很尴尬
This is gonna be so weird when they come down.
我们走吧 好吗 走吧
Let's just go. Okay? Come on.
等等 我饿了
Wait. But I'm hungry.
我们去买早餐 走吧 快走
We'll get breakfast. Let's just go. Come on!
走啊 快走
Let's go. Come on.
你们要去哪
Where are you going?
哪都行
Anywhere.
你妈妈在哪 我要跟她谈谈
Where is your mother? I need to talk to her.
我觉得这个时机不太合适
I don't think it's a good time right now.
她待在房间里不出来
She won't come out of her room.
她很郁闷 对吧
She's really upset, isn't she?
超郁闷
Big time.
你们怎么知道的
How'd you know?
我们打过电话来
We called.
告诉我她到底是怎么说的
Tell me exactly what she said.
我不知道 就听到她一直在叫
I don't know. There was just a lot of screaming.
发生这些事时 你爸爸在哪
Where was your father when all this was going on?
他就在她身后
Oh, he was right behind her.
擦不掉 擦不掉
Oh! It's not coming out! It's not coming out!
要吸干那些果汁 不要擦 要吸
Blot! Don't rub! Blot!
我们已经过了吸污和抹擦的阶段了
We are beyond blotting and rubbing.
就等着一身大汗和痛哭流涕了
I think we've moved on to sweating and crying.
好了 好了 不要慌
Okay, okay. Let's not panic.
我们就对艾米莉亚实话实说
We'll just -- we'll tell Amelia what happened,
然后由我们负担清洗费
and then we'll pay to have it cleaned.
米奇尔 万一这个洗不掉怎么办
What if it can't be cleaned, Mitchell?!
好吧 那我们就赔她一块新的地毯
Okay, okay. Then we'll pay for a new rug.
你疯了吧
Are you insane?
我在《建筑学文摘》中看到过
I saw it in Architectural Digest.
一块卖5万美元 戴安·基顿家里也有一块
It cost $50,000. It was in Diane Keaton's house.
不是 是那个 那个叫什么名字
Oh, no, it was in, oh, what's-her-name's house.
她演过《普里兹家族的荣誉》
Um, from "Prizzi's Honor".
还有这个这个 《阿达一族》
From -- uh, oh, oh, she was in "Addams Family".
你知道的 还有
You know, she --
是安耶利卡·休斯顿
Anjelica Huston!
对对对
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
天哪 一块地毯卖五万美金
Oh! Oh, my god. $50,000 for a rug?!
小卡 我们哪有那么多钱
Cam, we don't have that kind of money.
也许她不会让我们赔
Maybe she won't make us pay.
想想看 假如有人弄脏了我们的地毯
I mean, we wouldn't make someone pay
我们也不会让人家赔的
if this happened to us.
你没听见她在电话里说的话吗
Did you not hear her on the phone?
给我修好它 换掉它 开赔款支票给我
"Fix it. Replace it. Write me a check".
她可能已经把这句话绣到枕头上了
She probably has that embroidered on a pillow.
旁边就放了一罐人耳朵
Right next to a jar of human tears.
也许我们可以把它转一下[还有“逆转形势”的意思]
Maybe we can turn this around.
怎么弄 看上去就像有人在这流血了一样
How? It looks like someone bled out over here.
不 我说的是地毯
No. I mean the rug.
也许我们可以把整张地毯转一圈
Maybe we can turn the whole rug around,
把这块污渍放到沙发底下
put it under the couch.
明白了吧 没人会发觉的
See? No one would ever know it's there.
天知 地知 你知 我知
Well, you know, we would know.
那么
Well...
你在想什么
What are you thinking?
你不会想知道的
You don't want to know.
不 说来听听吧 因为我
No, tell me, 'cause I'm --
我觉得我们想得一样
I think I'm thinking the same thing.
我深表怀疑
I seriously doubt that,
因为我在想刚才那个应该是琼·柯林斯[美国女演员]家
because now I'm thinking it was Joan Collins' house.
好吧
Okay.
很好
Great.
歌洛莉亚 你 你来干吗
Gloria, what are you -- what are you doing here?
慢着 孩子们呢
Wait, where are the kids?
他们刚刚出去了
They just left.
他们跟我说你很郁闷
They told me that you were very upset.
-天哪 -你完全有权郁闷
- Oh, god. -And you have every right to be.
这件事太可怕了
It was bad.
我知道
I know that.
克莱尔 这只是个意外
Claire, it was an accident.
那也无法改变它所造成的伤害
That doesn't make it any better.
好吧 你说的没错 我了解你的感受
Okay, you're right. I know how you feel.
-天哪 -我也曾遇到过这样的事
- Oh, god. - It happened to me before,
不过是和另外一个女人
with another woman.
而且那次我是受害者["被上的那个"]
And that time, I was the one getting it.
那感觉真的很难过[真的很疼]
And it hurt.
很抱歉我如此直白
I'm sorry it had to come out like this,
但是你还是得承认
but you have to admit that you're only happy
只有当你是主导者的时候才会觉得开心
when you're the one cracking the whip.
你说啥
What?
别装了
Come on.
我们都知道菲尔是个妻管严
We all know how you ride Phil.
但是如果你能看开一点
But maybe if you just let go a little,
或许试着尝尝我的纸杯蛋糕["咪咪"]
maybe even taste my cupcakes,
我就会跟你一起参加糕饼义卖[我可以跟你们一起做]
I will join you.
使 使 使不得
No -- unh-unh. No. No.
我 我完全迷糊了
I-I am so confused right now.
我快晕过去了
I may pass out.
你在说什么呢
What are you talking about?
你又是在说什么
刚刚孩子们走进卧室
The kids just walked in on
看到我和菲尔在床上 那个
me and Phil I-in bed.
我们刚才在卧室里
And we've just spent the last hour
窝了一个小时
holed up in our room
考虑该跟孩子们说什么
trying to figure out what to say to them.
我刚才说的就是这个
That's what I'm talking about.
可以用下你的电脑吗 我要查一下邮件
Can I use your computer? I just need to check one e-mail.
可以 电脑在厨房里
Yeah, the kitchen.
歌洛莉亚 我刚才换了下一个航班
Gloria, I just switched us to the next flight.
你们的事情都解决了吧
Now, did you guys get everything straightened out?
克莱尔心情不好
Claire is very upset
因为他们嘿咻的时候被孩子撞见了
because the kids just walk in on them having sex.
天啊
Aw, geez.
好了 现在大家都知道了
Oh, then we're all up to speed.
她心情糟糕到没时间
She's so upset that she hasn't even had time
化妆和开电脑了
to apply her make-up or use her computer.
你们来这儿干什么 老爸
W-what are you even doing here, dad?
我觉得站在你的立场上
I don't think you should be the one
你没权利质问我了
doing the questioning here, missy.
干吗生她的气
Don't get mad at her.
你老婆刚才还要给我们吃她做的纸杯蛋糕呢
Your wife's the one who just offered up her cupcakes.
菲尔
Phil.
还好我们带了老妈的加油卡
Good thing we had mom's gas card.
不要让我后悔给你买了打火机
Don't make me regret buying you that lighter, dude.
收起来
Put it down.
好吧 我憋不住了
Okay, I'm just gonna say it.
我们的爸妈太不负责任了
Our parents are totally irresponsible.
我不是说我们撞见
And I'm not just talking about us walking in
他们刚才上演的那变态一幕的事
on their...little freak show earlier.
算了吧
Just let it go.
这怎么行 我们活着已经很幸运了
No. We're lucky to be alive.
他们有多少次让卢克在冬天
How often do they let Luke go -- go to school
穿短裤去上学
in shorts in the winter?
在我体重还没到六十磅的时候
And they let me ride in the front seat
他们就让我坐汽车前座
before I was 60 pounds.
还有我们很小的时候
And they never shut the gate
他们从来不关顶楼的门
at the top of the stairs when we were babies.
你记得你摔地上碰了多少次头吗
Do you know how many times you fell on your head?
记得吗
Do you?
记不得
No.
我们明白你的意思 他们这样确实不太好
We get it -- it was bad.
但是 我
But, you know, I --
我觉得
I guess...
总比一天到晚都吵架的家长好吧
it's better than having parents who fight all the time.
也许吧
Maybe.
我朋友杰克布的父母离婚了
My friend Jacob's parents are getting divorced.
他必须搬出现在的房子
He has to move out of his house.
他们上个礼拜才告诉他
They told him last week.
真惨
That sucks.
他很快就会习惯了
He'll get used to it.
我有一半的朋友父母都离婚了
Half of my friends' parents are divorced.
我朋友也是
Mine too.
这世界太疯狂了
It's insane.
这么说来 爸妈依然嘿咻 这是件好事
So it's a good thing mom and dad still do sex.
总比老妈忘了关火炉好
Better than mom leaving the stove on,
她这个月已经忘了两次了
which she's done twice this month.
我才发现事情还没到达
I just realized we haven't even gotten
最糟糕的情况
to the worst part of it yet.
最糟糕的情况是什么
Which is?
他们可能会跟我们谈这件事
They're gonna want to talk about it.
也有可能不会
Well, maybe not.
你开玩笑吧
Are you kidding?
他们的家长以前啥都没跟他们谈过
Their parents never talked about anything,
所以他们现在什么都要跟我们谈
so they want to talk about everything.
也对 就为了改喝脱脂牛奶这件事
Yeah, they called a family meeting
他们还特别召开了一次家庭会议
when we switched to 1% milk.
我不知道那几个孩子去哪了
I don't know where those kids are.
还有什么比在卧室门上
What is more important
装一把好用的锁更重要的呢
than putting a working lock on a bedroom door?
你还好意思跟我讲大道理
You are one to talk.
你什么意思
What is that supposed to mean?
你不记得
You don't remember
我那次撞见你和老妈干那事了么
when I walked in on you and mom that time?
歌洛莉亚 我们可以走了吗
Gloria, can we please go now?!
你还是少在这扮清高了 老爹
So why don't you just get off your high horse, dad.
至少我在试图解决问题
At least I am trying to handle this
总比你俩当时的态度要端正
better than the two of you did.
我们当时怎么解决的
What did we do?
你兑了一杯鸡尾酒 然后就回屋了
You made gimlets and went back to your room.
那你说我们应该怎么办
What were we supposed to do?
你 你 你们可以跟我谈谈啊
You -- you -- you could have talked to me.
你可以关心一下我是否还好
You could have made sure that I was okay.
你想让我跟你谈吗
Want to talk about it?
好吧 我们谈
Yes. Fine.
你妈和我当时在看《哈特对哈特》
Your mother and I were watching
那一集里面有成人镜头
a particularly racy episode of "Hart to Hart".
斯蒂芬妮·鲍尔斯要当卧底 扮演应召女郎
Stefanie Powers had to go undercover as a call girl.
-够了 老爸 -还没说完呢
- Mnh-mnh. Dad. - Hang on.
如果你知道我很爱高筒靴
This whole story makes more sense
那么你就不会觉得那件事很诡异了
if you know I got a thing for thigh-high boots.
太恶心了 你害我失去了性趣
Oh, gross! Gross. You are ruining sex for me,
还毁了我对靴子的爱
and boots.
用得还顺手吧
Working okay for you?
对 对
Oh, yes.
我在给在哥伦比亚的兄弟发邮件
I was sending an e-mail to my brother in Colombia.
我在给他介绍克莱尔
Um, I was telling him about Claire.
我发现我还真是太不了解她了
You know, I realize there's so much I don't know about her.
像是 她最喜欢哪个单词
Like, for example, what is her favorite word?
或是她第一只宠物的名字
Or what was her first pet's name?
歌洛莉亚 我不是傻子
Gloria, I'm not an idiot.
你是想知道克莱尔的密码吗
Are you trying to get Claire's password?
好吧 没错
Okay, fine.
我错给她发了一些东西
I sent her something by mistake.
所以我要赶在克莱尔看到之前
I need to get into Claire's e-mail
进她的邮箱里把它删掉
to erase it before she sees it.
在我看到什么之前
Before I see what?
你好呀 克莱尔
Hola, Claire.
你好 歌洛莉亚
Hi, Gloria.
在我看到什么之前
Before I see what?
这太难启齿了
It's so embarrassing.
是这样的 我跟杰
You see, Jay and I --
是歌洛莉亚的裸照
It's a naked picture of Gloria.
没错
Yes.
裸照
Naked.
我本来是想发给杰的
I was gonna send it to Jay.
我在照片里是全裸的 正面全裸
You see everything. The whole body.
-我得坐会儿 -好吧
- I need to sit. - Okay.
老爸
Wow, dad.
你刚才还教育我要
So, you just got done giving me a lecture
锁好自己的卧室门
on the importance of locking my bedroom door
可其实你跑我家来是为了拿回
while in my house to retrieve naked pictures
你妻子不小心发给我的裸照的
that your wife accidentally sent me.
我也是刚意识到这件事有多讽刺
The irony is just occurring to me.
你干吗
What are you doing?
我要 删了它
What I'm doing...is deleting it.
干得好
Good for you.
我们去拉斯维加斯吧
Let's go to Vegas!
再见
Ciao!
帮我们个忙 别再照相了
Do us a favor -- no pictures.
歌洛莉亚 等一下
Oh, Gloria, listen.
我们得找个时间谈谈糕饼义卖的事
We do need to talk about the bake sale at some point.
我有一些担忧
I have some concerns.
-意料之中 -是啊 -走咯
- Of course you do. - Yes. - All right!
我们现在怎么办
What do we do now?
好吧 我很担心
Okay, I'm really afraid
我是想错了
of reading this situation the wrong way,
但是我有百分之八十的把握觉得你在勾引我
but I'm 80% sure you're coming on to me.
好吧 只剩百分之四十了
Okay, now...40%.
米切尔 我们得做出决定了
Mitchell, we need to make a decision.
那个计划很完美
It was the perfect plan.
把地毯转一下 她好几年都不会发现那块污渍
Turn the rug, and she wouldn't find the stain for years.
但是我们做不到
But we couldn't do it.
我们太诚实了
We're too honest.
生活中总会遇到那种能反映出你真实人格的时刻
There are certain moments in life that define you,
而这就是其中之一
and this is one of those moments.
实在抱歉 我这么久才回来
Oh, guys, I'm so sorry that took so long.
天啊 这是怎么回事呀
Oh, my god. What happened here?
这是杰克逊弄的
Jackson did it.
他抢了莉莉的草莓汁就开始喝
He grabbed Lily's strawberry juice and started drinking it.
什么
What?
我们还没反应过来 他就已经把它弄洒了
Before we could stop him, it was all over everything.
-天啊 天啊 -我们真是一对烂人呀
- Oh, my god. Oh, my god! - We are horrible people.
我只是跟着你说而已
I'm only following your lead.
是啊 还不忘在旁边添油加醋
Yeah, so close that you stepped on the back of my shoe.
-过来 杰克逊对草莓过敏 -什么
- Come here. Jackson's allergic to strawberries. - What?
他的喉咙会堵住
His throat will close up,
然后他可能会有过敏性休克
and he can go into anaphylactic shock.
我必须马上给他打针
I need to inject him right now!
你确定吗 我觉得他挺好的呀
Oh! Are you sure? He seems all right to me.
是啊 也许让他呼吸点新鲜空气就没事了
Yeah, maybe just get him some fresh air.
别说了 他很讨厌打针
Stop talking! He really hates this.
所以我要你们俩
And so I'm gonna need you
帮我按住他的胳膊和腿 好吗
to help me pin down his arms and his legs, okay?
-实际上 -杰克逊 宝贝儿
- You know what? - Jackson, honey,
很抱歉妈妈不得不这么做
mommy's so sorry to have to do this,
-阿米莉亚 -但是只会疼一下而已
- Amelia -- - but it's only gonna hurt for a second.
快按住他的胳膊
His arms!!
好的 快点 准备打了
Okay. Hurry. Here we go.
一 二
One, two --
-等等 -等等
- Wait! - Wait!
杰克逊没喝草莓汁
Jackson didn't drink the juice!
我踩到了丽丽的包 结果里面的一盒果汁掉了出来
I stepped on Lily's bag and a juice box fell and we panicked
我们吓坏了 因为我们听到你在电话里说的话
because we heard you on the phone
我们可赔不起琼·柯林斯[美国演员]的地毯
and we can't afford Joan Collins' rug!
我们真的非常非常抱歉 这感觉真是糟透了
We are so, so sorry. We could not feel any worse.
不 这下坏了
Oh, no. That's bad.
十九号
Number 19!
-十九号 -来了 来了
- Number 19! - Yeah. Yeah.
可以给我们几张纸巾吗
Oh, uh, can we have some napkins, please?
纸巾用完了
All out of napkins.
洗手间里有手纸 米切尔
Paper towels in bathroom, Mitchell.
他知道你的名字
He knows your name!
我就直说了
And, uh...I'm just gonna say it --
我为之前发生的事情感到非常抱歉
I'm really sorry about what happened.
我们 我们不是对那件事感到抱歉
Well, we're -- we're not sorry about what happened.
而是对你们看到了那件事而感到抱歉
We're sorry that you saw what happened.
好了 他们 他们明白的
Yeah, okay. They -- they get that.
这么说吧
Let's see.
没人愿意看见自己的父母
Uh, no one wants to see their parents...
-你的感官享受 -一丝不挂
- Your sensuality... - ...not dressed.
基本上 这事是两个成年人做的
Basically, it's two adults.
成年人
Adults.
就像是握手
It's like you're shaking hands.
但是握的不是手
But you're not using your hands at all.
我可受不了一大家子人坐在那谈论这种事
I can't handle a big family talk about this.
我们别无选择
We're not gonna have a choice.
所以当他们谈的时候
So when they start talking,
我们就微笑点头然后想别的呗
just smile and nod and think about something else.
没错 这很容易 就像在学校上课一样
Yeah, it's easy. Just like at school.
所以 我想我要说的就是
So, I-I guess what I'm saying here
等你们长大了
is that as you get older
开始尝试自己的性行为时 你们会发现
and...explore your sexuality, you will discover
只要你们是和情投意合的成年人
that as long as you are in a committed relationship
建立了一段忠诚的感情
with consenting adults,
这件事就没什么好尴尬的
there's really nothing to be embarrassed about.
咱们都知道 只要我一展示我那结实的肌肉
And let's face it -- your mom can't keep her hands off me
你们老妈就对我爱不释手了
whenever the gun show comes to town.
说得好 老爸
Good one, dad.
幽默缓解了尴尬的局面
Humor makes difficult situations easier!
真的吗
Wow. Really?
绝对的
Totally.
你们像朋友一样跟我们聊天
You talked to us on our level
却又不失家长的威严
but without being condescending!
的确
We did.
很好
All right.
看来的确是这样
I guess we did.
咱俩真厉害
Yay, us.
我觉得咱俩真的处理得很好
I think we really handled that well.
我也这么想 你棒极了
Me too. You were excellent.
你也不错
You were pretty good.
今天真是太诡异了
Ugh, this is such a weird day.
我知道
I know it.
还要说一句
By the way...
结婚纪念日快乐
happy anniversary.
跟你结婚的每一天都很快乐
It always is.
妈 我能不能
Hey mom, can I get --
天啊 你们两个够了吧
Oh, my god! Enough!
这是什么
Hey, what's this?
你们的结婚纪念日礼物
Your anniversary present.
你们真是太贴心了
That's very sweet.
上帝啊
My goodness.
是什么
What is it?
门锁
A door lock.
真尴尬
How embarrassing.
谢谢你们
Thank you.
我们会每天都用的
We'll use it all the time.
我们觉得送锁给他俩是个好主意
We thought the lock was a really good idea.
可问题是 这东西上锁的时候有声音
The problem is it makes a noise.
还很大声
A loud noise.
在那以后我都很难面对老爸了
It's hard for me to look at dad afterwards.